{
    "id": "68a851654b8f431eaf2a1822a3bd6c25",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Each of these colors ………………………… you.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "suit",
                "suits"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. to the party.",
            "description": "Both is not used with 'not'.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither went",
                "Both didn't go"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "All of my friends ……………………….. arrived.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after all.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of these puppies …………………………. up for adoption.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of these roads ……………………….. to the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lead",
                "leads"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone of them ………………………… present there.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every, everyone, everybody.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let …………………………. get going.",
            "description": "Use the object form of the verb after let. ",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "us"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Your need is greater than ……………………………",
            "description": "Mine means my need. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "None of us ………………………….. seen him before.",
            "description": "We usually use a singular verb after none. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I like these …………………………… of movies.",
            "description": "Use a plural expression after these and those.",
            "answers": [
                "kind",
                "kinds"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "People starve when ………………………….. have no money.",
            "description": "Use they to refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "we",
                "you"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody wanted a drink, …………………………..?",
            "description": "In question tags, use they to refer to somebody, anybody and nobody. ",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}